goabroad.com 2018-01-27

# Privacy Policy | GoAbroad.com

By using or accessing GoAbroad.com or any GoAbroad LLC operated websites you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to all of the terms of this privacy policy, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the website. 

GoAbroad is a hyper-specialized search engine that connects future travelers to thousands of travel programs and opportunities offered by external organizations and companies worldwide. We do not provide international programs. 

Thanks to our **comprehensive program directories** and filters, our website helps make the decision-making process easier for travelers. Our travel program directories include: 

Each program directory also features verification levels, real participant reviews of programs, and past participant interviews to help travelers understand what the program experience is like on a deeper level. 

We also provide **resource directories and information** on [scholarships abroad](https://www.goabroad.com/scholarships-abroad), [embassies](https://embassy.goabroad.com/), [study abroad loans](https://www.goabroad.com/study-abroad-loans), and [travel insurance](https://insurance.goabroad.com/), as well as an [extensive article directory](https://www.goabroad.com/articles). 

In addition to our program and resource directories, we also offer **free tools** to help travelers choose an international program: MyGoAbroad and the GoAbroad Online Advisors. MyGoAbroad is a personalized dashboard whereby you can bookmark and compare programs side-by-side, save articles and resources, and organize your travel plans. Our Online Advisor Tool provides a platform for travelers to request customized advice on which programs from our database fit their expressed travel goals and interests. 

We are the **go-to website for travelers** to find all of the information they need to choose a program abroad. We take this responsibility very seriously, and therefore, continue to evolve our website offerings to meet the needs of the modern explorer. 

## Commitment

GoAbroad LLC ("GoAbroad") collects certain information about our users ("You") in order to make various features and functions of any GoAbroad operated website ("Site"). This personal information includes, but is not limited to, your first and last name, citizenship, travel interests, and your e-mail address ("Personal Information"). GoAbroad is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any Personal Information You share with us. GoAbroad established this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") so that You can understand the care with which GoAbroad intends to treat your Personal Information. 

## Use of Cookies

If you are browsing our website, you are anonymous to us, but we will still collect information like browser type and IP address. This data is collected for all GoAbroad visitors, is non-personally identifiable, and is used to manage, monitor, and track usage to improve our website’s services. 

However, if you sign up for a MyGoAbroad account, we store certain information from your browser using cookies to make higher quality recommendations based on your interests. In the same way, if you voluntarily provide data to us about your personal identification through any form or service on our website, you are no longer anonymous to us. 

## Third Party Advertising

GoAbroad may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner with partners and other third parties in order to present to members and other users of the GoAbroad website more targeted advertising, products, and services. We assure you that in such situations we will never disclose information that would personally identify you, unless you’ve agreed to have your information shared. 

## Disclosure of User Information

Except as otherwise stated in this privacy statement, GoAbroad will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by GoAbroad, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the GoAbroad Terms of Service or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of GoAbroad. 

## Privacy & Sharing of Contact Details

If you voluntarily use the GoAbroad Online Advisor Tool, the detailed program information matches we send to you is connected to outside organizations or institutions (“Providers”), so your contact information will be shared with the selected Providers so they can provide you with details about the opportunities that fit your interests. By clicking “Submit,” you automatically give GoAbroad.com permission to share your contact information with Providers that offer programs which fit your travel interests. If you voluntarily submit any type of Inquiry Form associated with a Provider on our website, the contents of your inquiry will be shared with the Provider so they can follow up with you to provide detailed information and answer your questions. GoAbroad.com is not liable or responsible for any communications between Providers and You following the submission of an Online Advisor Inquiry or Inquiry Form. 

## External Links

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of other websites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these external websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside websites. 

Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to any outside websites that have links on GoAbroad. 

## Confidentiality & Security

We use industry standard measures to protect all information that is stored on our servers and within our database. We limit access to this information to those employees who need access to perform their job function. If you have any questions about the security of our website, please [contact us](mailto:techsupport@goabroad.com). 

## Strict adherence to CAN-SPAM Act of 2003

Just like you, we hate spam. We have never sent spam or junk emails and our mailing practice strictly conforms to the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. However, if you willingly provide GoAbroad with your contact information / email address, we will send notices from time to time to your inbox based on the type of form you used to submit your contact information. This permission is expressed at each time of voluntary submission. 

## Newsletter

GoAbroad sends regular newsletters to all Users or Providers that subscribe through our website or any other online signup forms. These newsletters were created to ensure we provide the best possible service to our community. Subscribing to our newsletter also automatically puts you on our regular mailing list, which shares intermittent updates (i.e. contests) on company-wide announcements to our community. 

If you would like to subscribe, unsubscribe or update your preferences related to our newsletter or mailing list, click here. 

## MyGoAbroad

GoAbroad.com sends separate electronic notifications MyGoAbroad users who have voluntarily registered for an account at various time intervals. The full MyGoAbroad Terms of Service can be found [here](https://my.goabroad.com/terms-of-service). 

All email addresses associated with a MyGoAbroad account are also automatically added to our mailing list, which shares intermittent updates (i.e. contests) on company-wide announcements to our community. 

## Contests

GoAbroad.com sends individualized electronic notifications to entrants of any contest hosted on GoAbroad.com at various times. Each contest has a unique set of terms and conditions that all entrants should review prior to entering. The email addresses of all entrants are automatically added to our mailing list, which shares intermittent updates (i.e. contests) on company-wide announcements to our community. 

## GoAbroad Reviews

The GoAbroad Review Platform was created to provide users with access to honest first hand experience(s) and information about the international programs and Providers found on GoAbroad. To view our review policy, please click here. The email addresses of all reviewers is automatically added to our mailing list, which shares intermittent updates (i.e. contests) on company-wide announcements to our community. 

## Alumni Interviews

The Alumni Interview Form was created to provide users with a deeper look at what life abroad on a particular program looks and feels like from real participants, and also as a way for Providers to diversify the content hosted on their profile on GoAbroad.com. The email addresses submitted by all interviewees is automatically added to our mailing list, which shares intermittent updates (i.e. contests) on company-wide announcements to our community. 

## Inquiries

When users can voluntarily request information from Providers on our website through Inquiry Forms, the user information is shared with the selected Provider so they can contact the user at their discretion. GoAbroad does not guarantee a response or any outcome from each inquiry submission. Submitting an inquiry automatically adds inquirers to our regular mailing list, which shares intermittent updates (i.e. contests) on company-wide announcements to our community. 

## Contact Us Form

Users can contact the GoAbroad team for a variety of inquiries through our Contact Us Form. In these instances, user information is shared internally with our team to ensure the best team member can respond to your questions, comments, concerns, etc. Contacting us automatically puts you on our regular mailing list, which shares intermittent updates on company-wide announcements to our community. 

## License

You grant us, without any compensation of any kind to you or others, the right and license to use, copy, distribute, display, publish, perform, sell, sublicense, modify, edit, adapt, translate, transmit, created derivative works from, and otherwise exploit all Images and Videos in any form, medium or technology that we elect, whether now or in the future. Without limiting the foregoing, you agree that, without further approval from you, we may exercise the rights you grant us herein for any and all purposes we deem appropriate, including, without limitation, for the promotion, marketing, and publicizing of our services and products. The right and license you grant us is perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, unrestricted, and worldwide. 

By voluntarily submitting images and video to GoAbroad through any form, contest, or tool, you affirm, represent and warrant to us: 

  * You are at least 18 years old.
  * The User Information you provide to us true and accurate.
  * You haven’t impersonated any person or falsely stated or misrepresented your affiliation with a person or entity.
  * You own or have all necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to use and submit to us the Images and User Information and to authorize us to use the Images and User Information as expressed in these Terms and Conditions.
  * Your agreement to these Terms and Conditions does not in any way conflict with any existing legal agreement or commitment on your part to any third party.
  * Your images and User Information do not embody, reflected or reveal any confidential information and that we are not obligated to treat them as confidential.

These Terms and Conditions and any other legal notices published by GoAbroad on the Website, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and GoAbroad concerning the Website, your use of GoAbroad and any Content. If any provision of these Terms is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any one provision set forth in these Terms shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision, and GoAbroad’s failure to assert or enforce any right or provision under these Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. 

## Indemnification

You agree to indemnify and hold harmless GoAbroad and its principals, shareholders, agents, officers, directors, consultants, and employees from or against third-party claims, damages, payments, deficiencies, fines, judgments, settlements, liabilities, losses, costs, and expenses arising from or relating to any third-party claim, suit, action or proceeding arising out of the breach of GoAbroad’s representations and warranties contained herein. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

GoAbroad reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. If we make any material changes, a prominent notice will be posted on our website. You should visit this Web site from time to time to review the current Policy because it is binding on you. If you object to any such changes, you may cease using our website. Continued use of GoAbroad following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

If you have any questions about these Terms & Conditions, please contact us.
